quiz = [
  {
    "correctAnswer": "Papa",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Pear",
      "Peer",
      "Peeler"
    ],
    "question": "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter P?",
  },
  {
    "correctAnswer": "12 Drummers Drumming",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "12 Lords a Leaping",
      "12 Maids a Milking",
      "12 Swans a Swimming"
    ],
    "question": "In the song \"The Twelve Days Of Christmas\", what did my true love give to me on the 12th day?",
  },
  {
    "correctAnswer": "Fort Knox",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Fort Box",
      "Fort Dox",
      "Fort Stox"
    ],
    "question": "Where is most of America's gold located?",
    
  },
  {
    "correctAnswer": "Lima",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Lame",
      "Loan",
      "Love"
    ],
    "question": "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter L?",
    
  },
  {
    "correctAnswer": "Cacophony",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cabotage",
      "Gardyloo",
      "Halfpace"
    ],
    "question": "Which word is defined as 'a harsh, discordant mixture of sounds'?",
    
  },
  {
    
    "correctAnswer": "Atmospheric Pressure",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Humidity",
      "Room Temperature",
      "Salt in sea water"
    ],
    "question": "What is a barometer used to measure?",
    
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "6239f8109129041bf3925cc3",
    "correctAnswer": "Golf",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Garden",
      "Guard",
      "God"
    ],
    "question": "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter G?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950336",
    "correctAnswer": "Queen Victoria",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "James VI",
      "Elizabeth I",
      "George II"
    ],
    "question": "Who was the first English monarch to have a Christmas tree?",
    "tags": [
      "christmas",
      "uk",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951063",
    "correctAnswer": "Experience",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Expertise",
      "Extra Power",
      "Express"
    ],
    "question": "What Does The XP In The Operating System 'Windows XP' Actually Stand For?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c3d7cc59eab6f951b9c",
    "correctAnswer": "South Pole",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "The Peak of Mount Everest",
      "The Moon",
      "The Mariana Trench"
    ],
    "question": "In 1911 Roald Amundsen became the first person to reach where?",
    "tags": [
      "people",
      "firsts",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c367cc59eab6f950096",
    "correctAnswer": "10",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "12"
    ],
    "question": "What Is The Value Of The Letter Q In Scrabble",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge",
      "games"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc7d",
    "correctAnswer": "Gibberish",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Gobbledygook",
      "Blatherskite",
      "Flummox"
    ],
    "question": "Which word is defined as 'unintelligible or meaningless speech'?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc8c",
    "correctAnswer": "Conjubilant",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Jentacular",
      "Discombobulate",
      "Whippersnapper"
    ],
    "question": "Which word is defined as 'shouting together with joy'?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951074",
    "correctAnswer": "Xenon",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Halogen",
      "Neon",
      "Radon"
    ],
    "question": "What chemical element gets is name from the greek word meaning 'stranger'?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c357cc59eab6f94fc8a",
    "correctAnswer": "Discombobulate",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Cacophony",
      "Dragoman",
      "Dragoman"
    ],
    "question": "Which word is defined as 'to disconcert of confuse'?",
    "tags": [
      "words",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95045c",
    "correctAnswer": "7 Swans A Swimming",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "7 Maids a Milking",
      "7 Lords A Leaping",
      "7 Drummers Drumming"
    ],
    "question": "What did my true love give to me on the \"Seventh\" day of Christmas\"?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "6239f8351bb3145a698af015",
    "correctAnswer": "Tango",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Treat",
      "Turn",
      "Tumble"
    ],
    "question": "What word is used in the NATO Phonetic Alphabet for the letter T?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951012",
    "correctAnswer": "Otter",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Squirrel",
      "Turtle",
      "Bear"
    ],
    "question": "What Sort Of Animal Was Tarka?",
    "tags": [
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c377cc59eab6f95044b",
    "correctAnswer": "Tax evasion",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Murder",
      "Fraud",
      "Bribery"
    ],
    "question": "Gangster Al Capone, boss of the Chicago underworld, was finally jailed for 11 years for what crime?",
    "tags": [
      "crime",
      "usa",
      "chicago",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "id": "622a1c3a7cc59eab6f951043",
    "correctAnswer": "Lesser Lion",
    "incorrectAnswers": [
      "Iron Lion",
      "Ferocious Lion",
      "Brave Lion"
    ],
    "question": "What is the meaning of the name of the constellation Leo Minor ?",
    "tags": [
      "astronomy",
      "names",
      "general_knowledge"
    ],
    "type": "Multiple Choice",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "regions": [],
    "isNiche": False
  }
]

score = 0


for question in quiz:
    print(f"\n Score: {score} \n")
    print(question["question"])
    possible_answers = question["incorrectAnswers"]
    possible_answers.append(question["correctAnswer"])
    for inx in range(0, len(possible_answers)):
        print(f"{str(inx)}. {possible_answers[inx]}")
    
    ans_input = input("Please choose an answer: ")
        
    if possible_answers[int(ans_input)] == question["correctAnswer"]:
        print("Correct!")
        score += 1
        continue
    else:
        print(f"\n Wrong, true answer was {question['correctAnswer']}")
